The Ultimate Nightmare Documentary
Never Sleep Again: The Elm Street Legacy is a
documentary film directed by Andrew Kasch.
For decades, Freddy Krueger has slashed his way through the dreams of countless youngsters, scaring up
over half a billion dollars at the box office across eight terrifying, spectacular films.
Self, played by Heather Langenkamp.
Self, played by Robert Englund.
Self, played by Wes Craven.
Self, played by Robert Shaye.
Self, played by Lisa Wilcox.
Self, played by John Saxon.
Never Sleep Again: The Elm Street Legacy is a 2010 American direct-to-video documentary film that
chronicles the entire Nightmare on Elm Street franchise, except for the 2010 remake.
The documentary also explores the rise of New Line Cinema.
Written by Thommy Hutson, produced by Daniel Farrands and Thommy
Hutson, and co-directed by Daniel Farrands and Andrew Kasch.
Heather Langenkamp, who portrayed Nancy Thompson in three of the Nightmare
films, served as the project's executive producer and narrator.
As of February 2019, the documentary has grossed over $400k from video sales.
The film explores themes of movie business, behind the scenes,
special effects, horror filmmaking, celebrity interview.